Guide to The Adrian Flannelly Show Audio Recordings AIA.089
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- The Adrian Flannelly Show, 1978-2000; 256 audiocassettes in 4 flatboxes and 2 record cartons
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, September 9, 2000 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0238)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, September 16, 2000 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0239)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, September 23, 2000 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0240)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, September 30, 2000 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0241)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, October 7, 2000 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0242)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, October 14, 2000 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0243)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, October 28, 2000 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0244)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, November 4, 2000 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0245)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows - WLUX #1, November 11, 2000 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0246)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows - WLUX #2, November 11, 2000 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0247)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows - WLUX #1, November 18, 2000 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0248)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows - WLUX #2, November 18, 2000 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0249)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, November 25, 2000 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0250)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, December 2, 2000 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0251)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, December 9, 2000 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0252)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, December 16, 2000 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0253)
  - A. Flannelly/B. Maxwell (22'), undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0254)
  - A. Flannelly/J. Roach (A.O.H.), undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0255)
  - Adrian Flannelly Interview, undated (Box 7, Audiocassette 089.0256)
  - Demo Tape of Adrian Flannelly Shows, undated (Box 7, Audiocassette 089.0298)
- Additional Tapes, 1976-2001; 71 audiocassettes in 1 flat box and 2 record cartons
  This series contains 71 audiocassettes donated by Flannelly whose association with his radio program is unclear.
  - Ireland Xmas - Fintans House, 1976 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0257)
  - No Guests, November 1977 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0258)
  - Easter Sunday, Irish Ballet & Frank Durkin, April 15, 1979 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0259)
  - Christmas Greeting, December 20, 1981 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0260)
  - Vlichy Carter, 1983 (Box 7, Audiocassette 089.0261)
  - PFB, August 15, 1983 (Box 7, Audiocassette 089.0262)
  - Sound Check - Trish, March 1983 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0263)
  - Ballyohoneen, 1984 (Box 7, Audiocassette 089.0264)
  - No Guests, July 1984 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0265)
  - Dermot O'Brien (Great Irish Fair), September 1985 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0266)
  - APF, October 12, 1985 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0267)
  - Guss Hayes, January 1986 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0268)
  - Irish Ambassador Padriac McKiernan, Hal Roach, January/February? 1986 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0269)
  - Malachy-Brendan Shine, February 1986 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0270)
  - Malachy-Frank Patterson, Suzanne Stein, February 1986 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0271)
  - Aircheck, March 9, 1986 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0272)
  - Dearie - Pat McGuigan-Jimmy Kelly-Malachy, May 1986 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0273)
  - Malachy, May 1986 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0274)
  - Untitled, May 25, 1986 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0275)
  - Trish - Cadrian in Ireland, Frank Noland/Mattie Connolly, July 1986 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0276)
  - Stockton Wing. Peter Barry, September 1986 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0277)
  - Jim Flavin - Lottery - Visas, Eamon Doran, December 1986 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0278)
  - Freddy White, Paddy Noonan, Noel Kingston, Ed McKenna - Irish Center, December 6, 1986 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0279)
  - Maureen O'Hara, January 1987 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0280)
  - Flavin.Visas.Ray Collins, February 1987 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0281)
  - Charles Haughey Interview, April 20, 1988 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0282)
  - Liveline, May 27 1988, May 30 1988 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0283)
  - Gay McIntyre, October 30, 1988 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0284)
  - Untitled, January 1989 (Box 7, Audiocassette 089.0285)
  - St. Patrick's Day, March 17, 2000 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0286)
  - Untitled, October 21, 2000 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0287)
  - 1:20, December 30, 2000 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0288)
  - 1:20 #2, December 30, 2000 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0289)
  - :60 #3, December 30, 2000 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0290)
  - Untitled #1, January 6, 2001 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0291)
  - Untitled #2, January 6, 2001 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0292)
  - Untitled #3, January 6, 2001 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0293)
  - Adrian on Local Radio - Ballina, undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0294)
  - Barry Moore, undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0295)
  - Brian Murphy, undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0296)
  - Catholic Charities PSAs 60-50-30, undated (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0297)
  - Dukakis lined up for Adrian, undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0299)
  - Excerpt Mayor of Derry, undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0300)
  - Extract from MWR + NWR "The Rambling House", undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0301)
  - Gay Byrne Show, undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0302)
  - Glen Miller/G. Gershwin/L. Ronstat, undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0303)
  - Haughey, undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0304)
  - Haughey Dimaur NY, undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0305)
  - J Bastable/ An Hengas, undated (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0306)
  - Kennedy Hearings, undated (Box 7, Audiocassette 089.0307)
  - Noon, undated (Box 7, Audiocassette 089.0308)
  - Old Flames R.I.P., undated (Box 7, Audiocassette 089.0309)
  - Prime Minister Ireland/Garret Fitzgerald, undated (Box 7, Audiocassette 089.0310)
  - Ruthie Morrissey - Irish Soldier Boys, undated (Box 7, Audiocassette 089.0311)
  - Simple Mix Gold Dream, undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0312)
  - Untitled, undated (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0313 - 089.0314, Box 7, Audiocassette 089.0315 - 089.0328)